and may contain
mature subject matter.
Viewer discretion
is advised.
aAll singing:in
Boob world, boob world.
It's a world for you,
but it's actually two.
Boob World!
I gotta say, Morty, it's weird
that you wanted me to come,
but I'm actually
exstyched about it --
that's excited, stoked,
and psyched.
I didn't want you to come.
Talk to Rick.
Truth is, Summer, Boob World's
been at the center
of a few protests every day
for 30 years,
so they've recently rebranded as
a boob empowerment experience,
and if we bring a female,
we get in for free.
So, I'm, like, what, a Coke can
you're taking to Six Flags?
No, 'cause once you
get into Six Flags,
you can throw
your Coke can away.
No fucking way.
It can't be.
Holy shit, holy shit, holy shit.
Oh, look at that.
-What is it?
-It's a GoTron ferret.
It's not a GoTron ferret,
Morty.
It's the blue
GoTron ferret.
Boob World is canceled.
No, Rick, no.
You promised.
You always do this.
Tell you what, Morty,
I'll let you choose.
Do you really think
Boob World -
Yes.
Let me finish.
Is more important --
Yes.
Let me finish!
Than have all five
of the only five GoTron ferrets
in the universe?
Are you finished?
Yes. So, let's go.
Summer, help me hook the winch
up to the ferret.
Sure.
What the hell?!
You said you were
letting me choose.
Yeah, whether to break
my fucking heart.
You chose badly.
Morty:
That's how it all began.
To my sister,
it was just another game.
But what she
didn't know --
Summer: That was the moment
everything changed.
Morty:
Wait. What?
I had gotten my first taste of
respect and my first voiceover.
I can hear you.
Can you hear me?
And I knew then and there
I wanted more of both.
Hello?
Beth, Jerry,
do something fun with us.
A giant monster is attacking
in the Nibblenug system.
Your suits
are in the bathroom.
Mine smells skeletony.
I have a chiropractor
appointment.
What are you
involving us in?
Rick's been collecting
GoTron ferrets,
and now that he has all five,
we can combine them into --
Morty, for Christ's sake
spoilers.
Spoilers, Morty.
WE don't need
to sell this to anyone.
There's a giant
monster attacking.
In the Nibblenug system.
Since when does this house
care about alien lives.
We don't even watch
British television.
Told you. Let's just get
Gene from next door
and a homeless guy.
No. Hold on.
Fuck Gene.
Fuck the homeless.
Your kids and their grandpa
are asking you to do
an activity with them.
When did that stop being
a parent's wettest dream?
I guess around the time
our family created
a giant incest baby,
and the government
launched it into space.
Oh my God, we made a giant
incest baby.
Oh my God,
you might be a clone.
I exist because you guys
failed to abort me.
We get the family we get,
not the one we want.
And if you want to keep
the one you got,
get your asses into
some anime spacesuits.
-Fair enough.
-Okay.
Good work, Summer Camp.
Yeah.
I'm exci-toked
about this.
Sure you are -- now.
Morty:
Something new was forming,
and I was at the bottom of it.
Summer:
I let Morty have his voiceover.
It's really all he had left.
Okay, can you hear me
or not?
Do you mean can I, Summer,
hear you?
No. My voiceover
can hear your voiceover.
What's the difference?
One would be telepathy,
dumbass.
Now what?
Now, we --
All:
Go, Team GoTron!
Where are we zip-lining through
futuristic metallic tunnels to?
Each robot ferret is at a
different location on Earth.
You're going to the center
of a volcano.
Thank you?
Okay, well,
this isn't not fun.
Regroup on me.
I'll shoot a portal
to Nibblenug.
Did I just monorail
from my kitchen to Hawaii
just to regroup in outer space
above my kitchen?
Uh, Summer?
It's cool, Dad. Shut up.
Everybody,
attack one at a time!
Is that
the best way to --
Tee up something awesome?
Yes. Follow me.
Guys, we did our best,
but there's only one hope.
Activating link-dock.
Inter-Morphs -- rad-ified.
PostiTrinos -- maximized.
Holy shit, I-I can't believe
this is working.
Go, go, team!
It's GoTron time!
Oh, my God.
Hell yes!
This is amazing!
Okay, now we can
knock it around a little bit,
but trust me, we're still
building to something.
How do we --
Just hit buttons.
we're too big to fail.
I kicked him!
That was me, right?
Morty: Uppercut!
I can't believe I almost
went to the chiropractor!
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
Form Luminous Energy Sword!
That's your ass,
Mamma Jamma.
Morty: These were
the good times,
when we felt like
we could do anything.
But anything
is never quite everything.
And pretty soon...
That was nothing -- nothing
compared to what we can do.
There are infinite universes
where I still don't have
all five ferrets.
Th-th-those versions of me
would do anything
to complete
their collections.
Okay, but Rick, remember what
you told me to remind you?
Sometimes, enough is...
Sometimes,
enough is enough.
Morty, what are you doing?
He gets obsessed, Summer -
When are you going
to find your shame?
I have more.
Grandpa just gave
everybody the high point
of their lives,
and before he did,
every single one of you
was trying to talk him
out of it.
Wait. Yeah.
Wha-wha-what the fuck!
Now, he says we can go higher,
and big surprise,
it's time to
drag him down again.
Well, I vote --
No voting.
No debate.
It's not a democracy.
It's a Rickpublic.
You're in or you're out.
Obviously, I'm in.
I never said I wasn't in.
Me, neither.
Tell us what we're doing next.
Uh, I want to put together
a cookout.
That's it? I was honestly
prepared to blow someone.
-Jerry.
-I said "prepared"
and "someone."
Morty: Rick invited five
versions of our family
from different universes,
each with incomplete GoTrons.
I didn't have anyone
to talk to,
since the other four Mortys
had been to Boob World.
Did you walk
on the beach?
The beach that's all boobs?
No, the beach
that's all sand.
Yes, the boob one!
Rick was in the garage with the
heads of the five families.
Ugh, and Summer.
Summer:
In that first sit-down,
it was Big Fat Rick,
Ricardo Montaya,
Hot Head Rick --
he got that name because he was
prone to dramatic outbursts -
and Lil' Ricky Wrap-it-Up,
who was always great
at the end of a meeting.
At the head of it all,
me and Grandpa Rick.
Now, don't get
me wrong, C137,
we're happy
for your good fortune.
But we did not
travel to your universe
just to have it rubbed
in our faces.
Come on, Big Fat Rick,
you know your face
is too small
to rub anything on.
My face is the same size
as yours.
Wow. Huh. Hold on.
I'll be damned.
You're so fat
you're an optical illusion.
Summer, give 'em the pitch.
We're offering to help
each of your families
complete their
full GoTrons.
In exchange
for some concessions.
Ever since I was a little boy
in the slums,
I have dreamed of having
a complete GoTron.
But concessions?
I hope you mean
the kind from a counter.
I hope she means
ice cream!
We'd like you
to relocate your families
to this universe,
and let me make some
modifications
to the GoTrons --
in the interest of us
all working together.
Want to know
what I think?
Sure, Hothead Rick, just don't
unexpectedly fly off the handle.
I think you guys
got a lot of nerve
acting better than us!
This is the family that made
a giant incest baby!
Had the government
launch it into space!
It's still floatin' around
out there somewhere!
Are we ever gonna
live that down?
If I get a full GoTron,
it won't be by kissing your ass,
it'll be by taking
what's mine -- yours!
Hey! Gross!
No need.
And you were driving...
a ferret?
We all are, moron!
Give me key!
You'll regret this,
you level-headed fucks.
Obviously, we predicted
that might happen,
which is why we have
Yo-Yo Rick on standby.
Anybody got beef
with Yo-Yo?
Some people think he's lame,
but to me,
he's lame in a cool way
because he owns it.
Cool. That concludes business.
Lil' Ricky Wrap it Up?
Raise 'em up, boys!
Oh-pah!
Summer: And so, we helped
our people find their ferrets.
How they got them,
not our problem.
Then, we got down
to business.
Here's how it worked --
if a giant monster
attacked your planet,
we all got the alert.
Man:
♪ Hey, hey, mama mia's ♪
♪ Got a plate of spaghetti
for the takin' ♪
♪ Papa pia's got a great big
robot that he's makin' ♪
♪ I got the moon
in both my eyes ♪
♪ You got a bowl of pizza pie,
hey! ♪
♪ A bit of pasta with some anime
combined, yeah ♪
We formed
five GoTrons.
And those GoTrons
formed the GoGoTron.
All: Go, GoGoTron!
Man:
♪ Take it away, boys! ♪
Rick: I will never
get sick of this!
If you were a giant monster
at that time, in our universe,
you never had a chance.
Man: ♪ A bit of pasta
with some anime combined ♪
♪ 'Cause we're two genres, but
each one is intertwined, yeah ♪
Mine needs a weapon
like a Yo-Yo.
And a Yo-Yo on the chest.
Are you listening to me?
I-I need you to respect
this partnership.
I kept Rick removed
from the ugly stuff.
If you got in his way,
I got you out of the way.
And that made more room
to move up.
The head of my right arm.
Morty: Me? I ended up the left
foot of the left foot --
I guess because our robot
didn't have an asshole.
Summer:
Well, it had one.
Bitch! When are you gonna
stop breaking my balls?
You win, okay?
We're not competing, Morty.
And there's your answer.
I could move you up if I could
trust you to put family first.
H-how is that
putting family first?
Show me all the blueprints!
I agree.
That's an issue.
Big Fat Rick, his flask stays
full or your locker gets empty.
Thanks.
I know it feels good
when he likes you,
but that doesn't mean
him liking you makes you good.
Solid babble, Morty -- like a
fortune cookie written by Borat.
Yeah, I'm not
as smart as you.
That's why I know
you know what I mean.
You mean, if I really
loved my family,
I'd give control of it back
to your jealous ass.
Green Ferret Four needs a wash,
and we're out of detergent.
I just bought a box.
And Grandpa snorted it because
you make him feel fenced in.
Rick: Sum-Sum?
Get two boxes.
one of the planets we saved,
and built a secret nightclub
on it,
a place no enemies
could find us --
unless you count
my brother.
Morty: I didn't even have
my own ferret anymore.
Summer made me
something called
an "associate
security chief" --
whatever the hell
that means.
Rick:
Look at this guy.
And look at this guy.
Look-look at this guy over here.
Oh, there she is!
My Baby Princess!
Get up here.
Stop the music.
This. Is. Our. Queef --
O-our Queen.
She saved my life.
She-she set me free.
We wouldn't have what we have
without this crazy bitch.
And she's got
a special announcement.
Summer, tell 'em wha-what
we talked about.
Now? I don't think --
Okay, I'll do it.
God damn.
Morty: The new job
did have some perks --
like, I got to be around
the night Summer realized
she was in
over her head.
Okay, I've got 90 extra ferrets,
which means I need 10 more,
and then four of you
get your own GoGoTron,
and 20%of you
get a GoTron,
'cause we're all gonna have
a fucking GoGoGoTron.
He's very excited.
Um...
Oh-pah!
I hate my family.
You should.
Get in.
How's it going with
your grandpa's compulsiveness?
Is your sister
still enabling it? Huh?
Who are you people?
Let's just say we're
the rightful owners
of these ferrets.
Then, why were they scattered,
and buried across the universe?
We mean in a more general,
cultural sense. Arrrgh!
What your Grandpa did
is called "appropriation."
Not cool!
Hunnnnngh!
Look, Morty,
we've been watching.
We know you're the one
that knows what's best.
Work with us
from the inside.
Help us take over
this operation.
We're literally designed for it.
Mm-hmmmmmm!
Nobody will know
it was you.
Then, you can get back
to what's important.
Are those Boob Bucks?
Legal tender at every kiosk
and ride! Huuunh!
I can't.
Summer's treating me like shit,
but she's still my sister.
That's really noble, Morty.
If you were in our family,
your loyalty would be rewarded.
But you're not in our family,
which means we can kill you.
Oh, yeah?
Morty: And sure enough,
just when I stuck my neck out
for the family,
it got stomped on anyway.
-Dad!
-Mom! Dad!
Hothead Rick, baby!
I set myself
up for that!
-What the hell happened?!
-Hothead Rick.
How did he get
so close to us?
Morty was supposed
to be security!
-Morty?
-I-I-I stepped away, alright?
But-but not to
let that happen!
Morty, we're not
attractive strangers
next to you
on a flight to Paris,
traveling alone
to get over a breakup,
so this is no time
to be coy!
-Oh...pah.
-Lil' Ricky.
I'm all wrapped up,
Summer.
Guys, I know you don't trust me,
but what have we become?
Why are we
doing this anymore?
Because it's fun,
you little rat.
Now go home,
and play video games
while we clean up
these bodies,
or your mother and I will hire
people to break your knees!
This is $16,000
we got from the deep state
for stepping on
that trailer park.
That should be enough for school
lunch and home repairs.
Now, I gotta
turn my back on you.
No!
Summer:
With Morty out of the way,
things were looking up.
But looks
aren't everything.
Hi, Summer. Um, my cockpit's
not getting Wi-Fi.
Dad, you know that's not
what I do around here.
Oh, I'm not your Dad.
I'm a version of him.
This is my first day here,
and I-I'm not sure
what you do around here.
Then fuck off.
Oh, fuck you.
Excuse me?
I want your ID.
Mom. Are you Mom? Can you
control your rookie Jerrys.
Sweetie, we're all
a little overwhelmed -
Good point.
You're not a war-time Mom.
Why don't you find
your version of Dad,
and take a break,
take a holiday.
I don't have time to wait for
your confirmation,
so let's just say,
if you're here in 10 minutes,
I'll have you removed.
And then, the GoTrons
make the GoTrons,
make the GoTrons.
Couple of snags, but I know
how to speed things up.
Remember when we talked about
how the best thing we could do
for the family is to recruit
outside the family?
Yes. Way ahead of you.
Summer, I want you
to meet Kendra.
She's from
a temp agency.
She's got an entire workforce
ready to go,
and all of them have previous
giant robot pilot experience.
So, we'll be ready to go
ahead of schedule.
Well, I don't know
about that but --
Well, Kendra knows. So...
So....
You here
to break my legs?
No. We're here to talk
shit about your sister,
because she just
fired us.
-You're kidding.
-Arrogant little bitch.
Should we clip her?
No. She's not worth doing time.
You wouldn't do time.
You brought her into the world.
So, I can
take her out.
You thought there was
an actual law?
It's a joke
mothers say.
What kind of fucked up world
have you been living in?
Uh, one where your mother
murdering you
isn't a
comedic premise?
Guys, there's a little
adjustment period,
but pretty soon, you're gonna
to return to normal,
and you're not going to
want to kill Summer.
You're not even gonna
be mad at her.
Nah, fuck her.
She's my enemy.
Should we kill ourselves, so we
can get to hell before her,
and hide near
the entrance?
I like that.
Rick fired me.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, baby?
What happened to us?
We lost our minds.
I did it.
Morty was right.
I got addicted
to making Grandpa happy.
It's only because
your Grandpa
inflates the value
of his happiness.
That's a good point.
I mean, look at me.
I'm easy to make happy,
which is why
nobody gives a shit
if I am.
I appreciate it, but there's
something else too.
I've been really sensitive
about family lately
because of something
I've been keeping secret.
Okay. Who's on
the Supreme Court,
and what state
do we live in?
It's been years
since I've thought about this.
No, I'm not pregnant.
But as you guys recall, and as a
lot of people keep bringing up,
Morty and I did accidentally
create a giant incest baby,
which the government
did launch into space.
And I'm not sure
how to tell you this,
but it is still alive, and I
have been in contact with it.
There were soldiers waiting for
me outside school last month.
They took me to the Pentagon,
and briefed me.
And from there, I was shuttled
to a secret base on Mars.
They had captured him,
and wanted to see
if he'd respond to me,
instinctively, being his mother.
And he sure did.
But what they didn't expect
was that I'd respond to him.
I was supposed to help
discipline him,
so they could turn him into
the ultimate weapon.
Instead, I trained him to love,
to believe in himself,
and finally,
to escape.
The government doesn't want
anyone to know it happened,
but it's only a matter of time
before the story comes out.
And when it does, all we're
going to have is each other.
And you guys are a couple,
and Rick has Morty,
but I'm the odd one out
So, I wanted to make sure
we stuck together.
But instead, I drove us apart,
and Rick replaced me
with an anime girl,
so all I've got is myself
and my giant, tortured,
government-trained rogue
incest monster baby
out there in space somewhere.
Oh, baby.
What the fuck.
And then, you have to wonder,
what else are they doing
with our taxes?
Wait. Summer,
what did you just say?
Morty, a lot.
He replaced you with
an anime girl?
Big eyes?
Plus signs for teeth?
Ends sentences with weird sounds
that don't fit?
Yeah. That's going to be
his whole crew now.
And they're about to run their
first test on the GoGoGoTron.
Those people want
to steal the robots.
Th-they're gonna kill Rick.
He's all alone.
We-we-we've got
to go save him.
Right.
Or... you know, fuck him.
I'm good with that.
Yeah, fuck him.
Guys, a great leader once told
me you get the family you get.
Rick:
Alright. It works. Now, we just
got to find a giant monster.
My sensors have
picked one up, Rick.
Okay. Okay
Lock onto its location.
Yeah, got it.
Oh, it's you!
Huh?
What the hell is this?
Thanks for making
the biggest robot ever, Rick.
We'll take it from here.
You little assholes!
You son of a bitch!
Lock a load, boys.
Say "hello"
to my little me.
Give up, old man.
The G3 is ours.
And last I checked,
your "family"
wasn't coming
to save you, hmm?
Giant Invest Baby:
Go go goo goo.
Holy mother of mercy!
My God.
It's beautiful.
Yeah! Family!
-Is that --
-It's exactly what
it looks like. Yes.
Congrats, man.
I see the resemblance.
Form the Energy Sword!
Activate the Goddamn sword!
Oh, man, the sword. Maybe we
didn't think this through.
They're not actually gonna
attack a space baby, are they?
I never thought I'd be
the one to say this,
but you need to watch
more anime, Mom.
Whoa, easy now,
Naruto.
Bahbah go bye-bye!
Kendra: What the hell
is wrong with you people?!
You just have
an incest space monster
in your back pocket, huh?
Welcome to
the Smith family.
Shit. Put that down, Naruto.
Your great-grandpa is in there.
What do you say?
One last zipline?
Incest space baby.
Nicely done.
Morty: After that, things pretty
much went back to normal --
some version of it, anyway.
Rick said GoTrons were lame
little kid bullshit,
and we never talked
about them again.
Summer:
Except all those gigantic space
bugs were still runnin' loose,
and there were no GoTrons left
to fight them.
Morty: Yeah, millions die
every day.
Summer: But you want to know
what they could never kill?
Family.
-Where's Jerry?
-Help!
Help! I'm still out here!
Morty: Yep, nothing's
more important than--
Hey! Hey!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Ugh!
And just like that, I knew
our goose was as cooked as --
Voiceovarians. Ugh.
♪ Magic sights,
exciting sounds ♪
♪ Come day or night,
and feel around ♪
♪ This is the world
for you ♪
♪ No matter where
you've ever been ♪
♪ This is the place
your life begiii-i-ins ♪
♪ Boob World ♪
♪ It's a world for you,
but it's actually two ♪
♪ Boob Wo-o-orld ♪
Samansky,
you're late!
Won't happen again, sir!
Bugs,. Look to your left.
Now, look to your right.
None of you are coming back.
Not one.
In the entire history
of this program,
not a single bug
has returned.
Alright. Bring it in!
What are we?
-Normal-sized bugs!
-What do we do?
-Travel through
an interdimensional
gateway to a planet
with tiny people!
-Why do we do it?
-To spread the cure for AIDS!
Hey, Sarge, how do we know if
these little people
can understand us?
I mean, do these even
speak Buganese?
Funny, Palicki.
That's why we say it very loud.
Guys, you'll still be the same
civilized bug on their side.
It's not like
interdimensional travel
strips us of our clothes,
and makes us screaming monsters.
Or maybe it does.
It's impossible to know.
Now, get out of here!
My clothes --
where'd they go?
Man: Did you get any of that?